

# **KAREN ALMEIDA**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER STUDENT

### CONTACTS & SOCIAL MEDIA

Porto - Portugal

karenalmeida.lukiany@gmail.com

+351 932375354





## LENGUAGES:

- English (Between A2 and B1)
- Spanish (B2)
- Portugues (C2)

## **INTERESTS:**

- Hiking
- Travel
- · Appreciation for nature

### **ABOUT ME!**

During three years working in my field, psychology, I noticed the necessity to follow a new professional direction. So, I challenged myself to find something that I'd really like to do. To my surprise, I'm loving coding and developing websites! Every day I face new challenges and information. I want to continue exploring and growing on this new path.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **CONSULTANT**

UNASP-HT Oct 2020 - Feb 2021 Hortolândia-SP

#### CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGIST

Private Psychology Clinic Mar 2018 - Apr 2019 Hortolândia - SP

#### **HUMAN RESOURCES ASSISTANT**

Intituto Adventista de Tecnologia (IATec) Jan 2019 - Oct 2020 Hortolândia - SP

#### **CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGIST**

Faculdade Adventista de Minas Gerais (FADMINAS) Feb 2017 - Dec 2017 Lavras - MG

## **EDUCATION**

## CENTRO DE EMPREGO E FORMAÇÃO PROFISSIONAL DE VILA NOVA DE GAIA

Frontend Developer - Programação Web Jun 2022 - Mar 2023

## **UNASP - SP**

Bachelor of Psychology Feb 2012 - Dec 2016

## SKILLS:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Object Oriented Programming (OOP)
- Angular